

Junita Berglin

Linkedin: Junita Berglin/Linkedin
GitHub: Junita Berglin/Github

About: Driven by a passion for innovation and a keen interest in AI, I combine a creative mindset with technical skills and believe that is my strength. With knowledge of the multifaceted gaming industry, my experiences enrich my approach to user-centered design. My occupational therapy background has given me strong social skills and contributes to a refined aesthetic sense, ensuring that I deliver not only functional but also visually engaging digital solutions.



WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer Intern, StarStable, Stockholm Jan 2024 – ongoing. Working in frontend team with the website. Learned next.js and to use datoCMS. Creating generic sections and a quiz on the website. Working with agile methodologies.



Frontend Developer Intern, Stryda (G-loot), Stockholm Sept 2023 – Jan 2024 Created admin platform and tools in react, typescript and tailwind for the BI-team.



Occupational Therapist, Aleris AB Psychiatric care, Stockholm, 2016 - 2022

Responsibility: Working in a professional medical team together with psychologists, doctors and nurses to perform functional assessments, prescribe aids for patients with cognitive disabilities.

Occupational Therapist, Resursteamet (acquired by Nytida), Stockholm, 2016 *Responsibility:* Leading group activities for patients with cognitive disabilities.



Assistant Occupational Therapist, Afasihuset Sweden, Nov 2014 – 2015 *Responsibility*: Helping patients with aphasia in everyday life activities.





EDUCATION

Frontend Developer, Medieinstitutet, Stockholm, ongoing (aug 2022-june 2024)
Learning everything in web production from idea to finished website on different devices. This frontend Developer training gives me skills in javascript (typescript), css (scss), react, git and node – as well as practice in agile teamwork with sprints, working in Jira and with scrum methods!



Web development 1, NTI School, Sweden, remote course, 2021

Remote studies, Singapore, 2016 Psychiatry, advanced course Philosophy, basic course

B.Sc. in Occupational Therapy, University of Örebro, *Sweden,* 180 ECTS, *2013 - 2016* Major in occupational therapy with a bachelor thesis focusing on strategies for occupational therapists' to motivate patients with depression.



EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Occupational therapist, Järva Unga (addiction center), Stockholm 2020 - ongoing Helping young people with addiction in their every day life.

Fadder, Medical Student Network, Örebro University, 2014 Responsible for new students and organized various team building activities.



Telefon: 0735 45 60 64 **Email:** junita.berglin@gmail.com